Class of 1976 Records, 1972-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1976 Records
1972-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1976.
RG 80 UUID:adf25ddf-9268-4c8d-87cd-ed5f37fce194
4 boxes (1.25 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1976.
The Class of 1976 was the ninety-eighth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1976 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1976, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1976 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1976 (Box 2263, Folder 1)
- Commencement Speaker 1976 (Box 2263, Folder 2)
- Freshman Handbook 1972-1973 (Box 2263, Folder 3)
- Groups 1972-1976 (Box 2263, Folder 4)
- History 1972-1976 (Box 2263, Folder 5)
- Ivy Day 1976 (Box 2263, Folder 6)
- Last Chapel 1976 (Box 2263, Folder 7)
- Class Letters 1977, 1985, 2001 (Box 2263, Folder 8)
- Class List 1974 (Box 2263, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1981 (Box 2263, Folder 10)
- Reunion 2006 (Box 2263, Folder 11)
- Senior Photographs-unidentified (Box 2266, Folder 1)
- Senior Photographs-A-B (Box 2266, Folder 2)
- Senior Photographs-C-E (Box 2266, Folder 3)
- Senior Photographs-F (Box 2266, Folder 4)
- Senior Photographs-H-K (Box 2266, Folder 5)
- Senior Photographs-L-M (Box 2266, Folder 6)
- Senior Photographs-N-Q (Box 2266, Folder 7)
- Senior Photographs-R-S (Box 2266, Folder 8)
- Senior Photographs-T-Z (Box 2266, Folder 9)